http://www.calicopie.co.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Our privacy policy sets out what personal buyer information we receive, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties. We abide by and are compliant with the Data Protection Act 1998 (herein referred to as “The DPA”) and the General Data Protection Regulation (herein referred to as “The GDPR”) which came into effect on 25th May 2018. We are committed to keeping buyers’ personal information secure and confidential.Lawful Basis for Processing Personal DataWe process all personal data lawfully, fairly and in a transparent manner. Processing is necessary in order to fulfil buyer orders and enquiries. We retain information provided, such as transaction information for internal financial accounting purposes. It is a legal requirement to retain this information for a period of 7 years.Data We Receive: Personally Identifiable InformationWe receive personally identifiable information only when it is voluntarily submitted by buyers when placing an on-line order. The data we receive includes: name, address, delivery name, delivery address, e-mail address, telephone number, date of order, items ordered, value of items ordered, chosen method of delivery. We do not sell or rent personally identifiable information to any third party for any purpose.How we use buyers’ personal informationWe may use any personal buyer information to:•	process and dispatch buyers’ order/s•	carry out regulatory checks to meet our legal obligations•	prevent and detect crime•	develop and improve our products•	undertake anonymised statistical analysis (we won’t be able to identify individuals from this data)We treat all information we hold about buyers as private and confidential. We will not reveal any personal details or details concerning buyers’ orders to anyone not connected with us, unless:•	a buyer asks us to reveal the information, or we have a buyer’s permission to do so•	we are required or permitted to do so by law•	it is required by law enforcement, fraud prevention or credit reference agenciesWe may share buyer personal information with our suppliers, service providers and other contractors only to fulfil orders buyers place with us.If an item is claimed as not received we will make a claim against the Royal Mail who will investigate why the item was not delivered, this will entail giving your personal details including but not limited to your name and address.Data Subject Access RequestsUnder the GDPR buyers are entitled to obtain from us a copy of the data held concerning them and to have any inaccuracies in the data rectified. We are obliged to provide this data to within 1 calendar month of the request and free of charge. However we have the right to refuse or charge for requests that are manifestly unfounded or excessive and repetitive. We do not hold, or have any access to, any details of credit cards, debit cards or PayPal accounts.Privacy PolicyWe do not disclose any of your information to third parties. Calico Pie does not have access to any of your credit/debit card or PayPal account details. Your contact details will only be used to process your order.Access rights You have a right to access the personal data that is held about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information Calico Pie holds about you, please write to us at the address given on the web site enclosing your postal details.
Privacy Policy
